Arthur J. Finkelstein Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Personal File, 1960-2013 (Box 138-139)
  - Conservative literature, 1964-1967, (2 folders) (Box 138)
  - Essex Greenbelt Association, 1991 (Box 138)
  - Family miscellany, 1985-1988, 1994, 2002-2005 (Box 138)
  - Horse racing, 1983-2004 (Box 138)
  - Keepsakes, circa 1964-1965, circa 1978-2013, (2 folders) (Box 138)
  - Master's program exam, 1968 (Box 139)
  - Mayoral election, 1968-1969 (Box 139)
  - The Phoenix, 1965-1966 (Box 139)
  - School work, circa 1965 (Box 139)
  - Wedding, 2005 (Box 139)
  - Writings, 1960, circa 1965, (2 folders) (Box 139)
- Oversize, 1970-1986 (Box OV 1-5)
  Material includes Rolodex cards, a scrapbook page, and a campaign poster.
  Listed and described according to the series, subseries, containers, and folders from which the items were separated.
  - Consultant File
    - Buckley, James Lane
      - Scrapbook page, 1970-1971 (Container 7, Miscellany) (Box OV 5)
    - Shamie, Ray
      - Campaign poster, 1986 (Container 56, same heading), 1985-1987 (Box OV 5)
  - Alphabetical File
    - Rolodex cards, 1986 undated (Container 74, Contacts) (Box OV 1-4)
    - Richard Nixon thank you card, 1972, (Container 98, Photographs) (Box OV5)